

# Jihad Melhem

UI/UX Designer & Interior Designer



#### **Personal Information**

+961 70 599 077 jihad.melhem9@gmail.com <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Portfolio</u> Beirut, Lebanon As a professional with expertise in both UI/UX design and Interior design, I bring a unique set of skills to every project. I excel in creating user-centered interfaces that enhance the user experience and have a keen eye for detail. My deep understanding of spatial design enables me to conceptualize and execute both beautiful and functional interior spaces.

#### **Education**

Oct.2016 - Jul. 2021

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Interior Design Arts, Science, & Technology University In Lebanon

### Languages

Arabic: Native

English: Intermediate French: Intermediate

# Softwares and Tools













### Training & Certifications

UI/UX Design Bootcamp - SE Factory

Jul. 2024 - Sep. 2024

Completed an intensive UI/UX program covering the case study, principles of UI design, journey map, User low, competitor analysis, workshops, projects and the advanced level in figma, it's 6 weeks in addition to 2 weeks for the final project.

### **Project**

Coffee Delight Website

Jul. 2024 - Aug. 2024

The website is able to demonstrate a service for ordering coffee. Main Feature: The platform integrates a comprehensive network of nearby coffee shops, allowing users to conveniently order from the closest location, with a seamless process.

## **Work Experience**

Sales Associate | Aishti | Home Collection

Nov. 2022 - Jul. 2024

- Met with customers to discuss design concepts, materials, and pricing options.
- Provided customers with product knowledge and answered questions regarding pricing, delivery details, or repair services.

#### Cashier | Gray Mackenzie

Feb. 2019 - Feb. 2022

- · Handled cash, credit, or check transactions with customers.
- Scanned goods and collected payments.
- · Ensured pricing was correct.
- Issued refunds, or changed tickets, and provided receipts.